Finding Aid for Michigan Association for Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance records, 1946-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan Association for Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance records, 1946-2005
Michigan Association for Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance.
18 linear feet
85283 Bf 2
State organization founded in 1927 to promote physical education in schools and tring of Physical education teachers. Records consist of files and photographs relating to the administration and activities of the organization.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records of the organization were donated in a series of accessions beginning in 1982 (Donor No. 6860 ).
The collection is open to research.
Interest in physical education in Michigan schools has a long history extending back to the mid-nineteenth century. But it was not until 1911 that the Michigan State Legislature made the teaching of "physical culture" mandatory in city schools and colleges. In 1927, the Michigan Association of Health and Physical Education (which became MAHPER at some unspecified point in time, and Michigan Association of Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance in 1981) formed. It affiliated with the American Physical Education Association in 1930. By the late 1950s, a number of standing committees and regional representatives were established in order to better cope with an expanding membership and shifting professional interests. At this time, the first state conventions and professional workshops and clinics were initiated. The MAHPER Newsletter had been published since 1946; this became the MAHPER News in 1960, and expanded into the larger MAHPER Journal ten years later. In 1981, this became the MAHPERD Journal.
The aims of MAHPERD are to work with state and school officials to promote programs of physical fitness, and to train teachers of physical education. It also functions to advance the profession of physical training and as a clearinghouse for information on personnel and the status of physical education in the schools.
MAHPERD is affiliated with the national American Alliance for Health, Physical Education and Recreation, and is an associate member of the Michigan Educational Association. MAHPERD is organized into seven "divisions": Dance, Girls' and Women's Sports, Health, Men's Athletics, Physical Education, Recreation, and Students. The state is divided into six districts. Each division has its own vice-president, and each district has a president. Officers in the state organization include a past-president, a president, a president-elect, a secretary-treasurer, an editor, a membership secretary, an executive secretary and seven representatives to special organizations. Official business is the responsibility of the Board of Directors and a Representative Assembly.
The MAHPERD records consist of files and photographs relating to the administration and activities of the organization as it sought to promote the expansion of physical education and recreational activities in schools and communities across Michigan. The records were received in several accessions beginning in 1982 (boxes 1-7); 1988-1889 (box 8) and 1992 (boxes 8-9). The physical arrangement of the records reflects the accessions. There is some overlap and continuation of content between the accessions. The records have been arranged in the following series: History; Associated Organizations; Awards; Committees; Conferences and Workshops; Conventions; Correspondence; Finances; Girls and Women's Athletics; Meetings (includes Board of Directors and Executive Board); Publicity; Organization; Petitions and Position Papers; Projects and Special Interests; Publications; Reports, Scrapbooks and Miscellanea; Photographs; Presidents Files; Yearly Files; and Executive Director Files.
Researchers concerned with school curricula might use these papers to examine the conflicts and congruencies between physical training and specifically academic disciplines. Furthermore, there is ample material on women's athletics. From its inception, MAHPER seems to have had more egalitarian relations between the sexes than is the case in many professional associations; of the MAHPER presidents holding office between 1926 and 1962, nearly half were women. MAHPER has long been opposed to the second-rate physical education given to girls and young women. In sum, the primary interest of this collection is its documentation of shifting attitudes towards physical education both on the part of the general public and among professionals.
Subjects:
Dance.; Michigan Association for Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance.; Physical education and training.; Physical education for women.; Public health--Michigan.; Recreation.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Michigan Association for Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- History
  The series History consists of a brief history of MAHPER compiled in 1962 by the organization itself, a map delineating the six MAHPER districts, and an informational brochure on the purposes of the Association.
  - History and background files (Box 1)
- Associated Organizations
  Associated Organizations contains material on the relationship between MAHPER and a number of Michigan groups. These include the Council of State Organizations (COSO), the Michigan Educational Association (MEA), the Michigan Educational Research Council (MERC), and the Michigan High School Athletic Association. Other additional associated organizations may be found in the series Girls' and Women's Athletics.
  - Council of State Organizations (COSO)
    - Correspondence 1967-1976 (Box 1)
    - Minutes 1967-1976 (Box 1)
    - organization 1965-1968 (Box 1)
    - Miscellanea (Box 1)
  - Michigan Educational Association (MEA)
    - Coordinating Council
      - Correspondence 1970-1971 (Box 1)
      - Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 1)
      - Miscellanea (Box 1)
    - Health Council 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Educational Research Council (MERC) 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Michigan High School Athletic Association 1958-1961, 1979 (Box 1)
- Awards
  - MAPHERD Awards (Box 1)
- Committees
  - Blue Sky Committee 1980 (Box 1)
  - Certification Committee (Box 1)
  - Coaches Association Committee (Box 1)
  - Competency-Based Teacher Evaluation, Ad Hoc Committee for (Box 1)
  - 1976-1980 (Box 1)
  - Constitution Committee 1963-1974 (Box 1)
  - Crisis Committee 1972 (Box 1)
  - Executive Committee 1969-1980 (Box 1)
  - Executive Secretary, Ad Hoc Committee to Evaluate the Role of 1976 (Box 1)
  - Historical Records Committee 1920-1978 (Box 1)
  - Honor Awards Committee 1957-1977 (Box 1)
  - Image Improvement, Ad Hoc Committee for (Box 1)
  - Interim Health Education Planning Committee 1973 (Box 1)
  - Legislative Committee 1963-1976 (Box 1)
  - Lifetime Sports Steering Committee 1970 (Box 1)
  - Membership Committee 1959-1973 (Box 1)
  - Nominating Committee 1967-1980 (Box 1)
  - Outdo-or Education Committee 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - Past Presidents Committee 1969-1971 (Box 1)
  - Performance Objectives Committee 1980 (Box 1)
  - Physical Education and Health Education, Ad Hoc Committee on Clarification of the Relationship between 1968-1970 Physical Education Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 1)
  - Professional Growth Committee 1962-1970 (Box 1)
  - Publications Committee 1971-1977 (Box 1)
  - Recruitment Committee (Box 1)
  - Reorganization, Committee on (Box 1)
  - Resolutions Committee 1962-1972 (Box 1)
  - Restructure of MAHPER, Ad Hoc Committee for 1975-1978 (Box 1)
  - Special Committee for Appointments 1970-1972 (Box 1)
  - Standing Committees (Box 1)
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)
- Conferences and Workshops
  The Conferences and Workshops series includes both the programs and planning materials for the various conferences sponsored by the association.
  - 1949-1967 (Box 1)
  - 1969-1975 (Box 1)
  - Past Presidents Conference 1975 (Box 1)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- Conventions 1950s-1988
  Conventions is a fairly substantial set of files. It begins in the 1950s and ends in 1981, but the most extensive coverage is from the years 1969-1975. For these years, there is correspondence relating to the convention, material from the planning committees, financial considerations, and convention programs. There are two chronological runs of convention files, received in different accessions.
  - Conventions 1950s-1981
    - Undated and pre-1960 (Box 1)
    - 1960 (Box 1)
    - 1961 (Box 1)
    - 1962
      - Exhibits (Box 1)
      - Finances (Box 1)
      - Planning Committee (Box 1)
      - Program (Box 1)
      - Registration (Box 2)
    - 1963 (Box 2)
    - 1964 (Box 2)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 2)
    - 1968 (Box 2)
    - 1969
      - Correspondence
        - January-September (Box 2)
        - October-December (Box 2)
      - Finances (Box 2)
      - Planning Committee (Box 2)
      - Program (Box 2)
      - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1970
      - Correspondence (Box 2)
      - Exhibitors (Box 2)
      - Planning Committee (Box 2)
      - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1971
      - Correspondence (Box 2)
      - Planning Committee (Box 2)
      - Program (Box 2)
      - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1972
      - Planning Committee (Box 2)
      - Program (Box 2)
      - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1973
      - Planning Committee (Box 2)
      - Program (Box 2)
      - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1974
      - Correspondence (Box 2)
      - Planning Committee (Box 2)
      - Program (Box 2)
      - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1975
      - April 3-5, Midwest District Convention (Box 2)
      - October 17-19, State Convention
        - Planning Committee (Box 2)
        - Programs (Box 2)
        - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1976 (Box 2)
    - 1977 (Box 2)
    - 1978 (Box 2)
    - 1979 (Box 2)
    - 1980
      - Correspondence (Box 2)
      - Program (Box 2)
      - Miscellanea (Box 2)
    - 1981 (Box 2)
  - Conventions/Representative Assembly 1965-1988
    - 1966 (Box 7)
    - 1969 (Box 7)
    - 1970 (Box 7)
    - 1972 (Box 7)
    - 1973 (Box 7)
    - 1976-1979, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - 1981 (Box 7)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 7)
    - 1986-1988 (Box 7)
- Correspondence
  Correspondence spans the years 1960-1981. It is followed by Finances, which is further divided into Audits, Budgets, Ledgers, Reports, information on Tax Exempt Status for MAHPER, and miscellanea.
  - Undated 1960-1965 (Box 2)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - 1968 (Box 2)
  - 1969 (Box 2)
  - January-August 1970 (Box 2)
  - September-December 1970 (Box 2)
  - January-March 1971 (Box 2)
  - April-December 1971 (Box 2)
  - 1972 (Box 3)
  - 1973 (Box 3)
  - 1974 (Box 3)
  - January-March 1975 (Box 3)
  - April-June, 1975 (Box 3)
  - July-September 1975 (Box 3)
  - January-April 1976 (Box 3)
  - May-August 1976 (Box 3)
  - September-December 1976 (Box 3)
  - 1977-1979 (Box 3)
  - 1980 (Box 3)
  - 1981 (Box 3)
  - 1981-1987, 3 folders (Box 7)
- Finances
  - Audits 1961-1977 (Box 3)
  - Budgets 1960-1980 (Box 3)
  - Ledgers
    - 1962-1967 (Box 3)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - Reports
    - 1955-1965 (Box 3)
    - 1966-1980 (Box 3)
  - Tax Exempt Status
    - 1963-1970 (Box 3)
    - 1971-1976 (Box 3)
  - Miscellanea (Box 3)
  - AAPHERD Memos 1976-1983 (Box 7)
  - Reports 1960-1989 (Box 7)
- Girls' and Women's Athletics
  Girls' and Women's Athletics is one of the most substantial sections of the collection. The largest subdivision within it is the MAHPER Division of Girls' and Women's Sports. Here there are folders for Conferences and Workshops, Correspondence, Finances, Intercollegiate Competition, Minutes, Newsletters, Officiating, the Organization of the Division itself (its Constitution, Officers, Operating Codes, Policies and Structural Charts), Papers, Reports, Resolutions, and Miscellanea. Additional associated organizations to be found in this subdivision are the Michigan Board of the National Section on Women's Athletics, (an early organization, 1939-1953), the Michigan Girls' Athletic Association, and the Representative Council for Michigan Women's Intercollegiate Sports.
  - Division of Girls' and Women's Sports
    - Conferences and Workshops
      - 1960-1970 (Box 3)
      - 1971 Estes Park, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda
      - 1959-1969 (Box 3)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 3)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 4)
    - Finances
      - Budgets and Reports 1956-1976 (Box 4)
      - Ledger 1944-1963 (Box 4)
    - Intercollegiate Competition 1968-1970 (Box 4)
    - Minutes
      - 1957-1959 (Box 4)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 4)
      - 1962-1964 (Box 4)
      - 1965-1967 (Box 4)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 4)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 4)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 4)
    - Newsletters and Bulletins 1959-1964 (Box 4)
    - Officiating
      - Correspondence 1969-1973 (Box 4)
      - Lists of Women Officials (Box 4)
      - Surveys (Box 4)
      - Miscellanea (Box 4)
    - Organization
      - Constitution 1960-1968 (Box 4)
      - Officers and Board Members 1962-1968 (Box 4)
      - Operating Codes 1965-1972 (Box 4)
      - Policies and Procedures 1958-1966 (Box 4)
      - Structural Charts (Box 4)
    - Papers (Box 4)
    - Reports
      - Undated, and 1959-1972 (Box 4)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 4)
    - Resolutions (Box 4)
    - Miscellanea (Box 4)
  - Michigan Board of the National Section on Women's Athletics 1939-1953 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Girls Athletic Association 1972-1974 Representative Council for Michigan Women's Intercollegiate Sports, 1959-1970 (Box 4)
- Meetings
  Meetings is organized into annual meetings, annual Business Meetings, Board of Directors, Executive Board, General Board, and governing Board Meetings and Representative Assemblies. The latter includes not only minutes and reports, but also material concerning the planning of the Assemblies. Here one segment of material from the Midwest District of the AAHPER is included, since that Assembly was held in Michigan (1970).
  - Annual Meetings 1960-1967 (Box 4)
  - Annual Business Meetings
    - 1961 (Box 4)
    - 1962 (Box 4)
    - 1963 (Box 4)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 4)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Board of Directors Meetings
    - 1959-1963 (Box 4)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 4)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - 1971 (Box 5)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 5)
    - 1974 (Box 5)
    - 1975 (Box 5)
    - 1976 (Box 5)
    - 1977-1981 (Box 5)
    - 1949-1951, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 7)
    - 1960-1967, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - 1971-1988, 6 folders (Box 7)
  - Executive Board Meetings 1966-1972 (Box 5)
  - General Board Meetings 1966-1968 (Box 5)
  - Governing Board Meetings 1969-1972 (Box 5)
  - Representative Assemblies
    - 1964-1965 (Box 5)
    - 1966 (Box 5)
    - 1967 (Box 5)
    - 1968 (Box 5)
    - 1969 (Box 5)
    - 1970
      - MAHPER (Box 5)
      - Midwest District of the American Association for Health, Physical Education and Recreation (Box 5)
    - 1971 (Box 5)
    - 1972 (Box 5)
    - 1973 (Box 5)
    - 1974 (Box 5)
    - 1975 (Box 5)
    - 1976 (Box 5)
    - 1977 (Box 5)
    - 1978 (Box 5)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 5)
  - Motions and Resolutions
    - 1961-1973 (Box 5)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 5)
- Publicity
  - News Releases 1968-1973 (Box 5)
- Organization
  The Organization series is the largest in the collection. Organization is further subdivided into Constitutions (1947-1972), Districts, Divisions (the Division of Girls' and Women's Sports should be considered along with this category), officers, Operating Codes, and Regions.
  - Constitutions 1947-1972 (Box 5)
  - Districts
    - Operating Codes (Box 5)
    - Presidents (Box 5)
    - Reports
      - District I (Box 5)
      - District II (Box 5)
      - District III (Box 5)
      - District IV (Box 5)
      - District V (Box 5)
    - Representatives (Box 5)
  - Divisions
    - General Division 1967-1968 (Box 5)
    - Dance Division 1970-1976 (Box 5)
    - Girls' and Women's Sports- (Box 5)
      (see Girls' and Women's Athletics
    - Health Division
      - Conferences 1970 (Box 5)
      - Correspondence
        - 1970-1975 (Box 5)
        - 1976 (Box 6)
      - Policies and Papers 1970-1976 (Box 6)
      - Reports 1962-1980 (Box 6)
      - Miscellanea (Box 6)
    - Men's Athletics 1964-1971 (Box 6)
    - Physical Education Division
      - Correspondence 1969-1976 (Box 6)
      - Reports 1961-1980 (Box 6)
      - Miscellanea (Box 6)
    - Recreation Division 1964-1976 (Box 6)
    - Student Division
      - Conferences and Workshops 1964-1965 (Box 6)
      - Correspondence 1965-1976 (Box 6)
      - History 1962-1965 (Box 6)
      - Minutes 1963-1967 (Box 6)
      - Newsletter 1964-1966 (Box 6)
      - Operating Code 1963-1964 (Box 6)
      - Miscellanea (Box 6)
  - Membership
    - Correspondence 1958-1976 (Box 6)
    - Procedures (Box 6)
    - Promotion (Box 6)
    - Reports and Statistics
      - 1958-1962 (Box 6)
      - 1963-1980 (Box 6)
  - Officers
    - Board of Directors
      (see also "Meetings")
      - Correspondence
        - 1965-1971 (Box 6)
        - 1972-1981 (Box 6)
      - Operational Chart 1961-1962 (Box 6)
      - Rosters 1961-1978 (Box 6)
    - Candidates for Office 1963-1976 (Box 6)
    - Executive Secretary
      - Establishment of the Position 1964-1973 (Box 6)
      - Reports 1970-1979 (Box 6)
    - Handbooks
      - 1960-1961 (Box 6)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 6)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 6)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 6)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 6)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Past Presidents (Box 6)
    - President
      - 1926-1970 (Box 6)
      - Reports 1951-1976 (Box 6)
    - President-Elect 1971-1976 (Box 6)
    - Secretary-Treasurer 1961, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Miscellanea (Box 6)
  - Operating Codes
    - Undated (Box 6)
    - 1957-1964 (Box 6)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 6)
    - Miscellanea (Box 6)
  - Regions (Box 6)
- Petitions and Position Papers
  - Petitions 1962-1973 (Box 6)
  - Position Papers 1962-1976 (Box 6)
- Projects and Special Interests
  The Projects and Special Interest series includes files on a number of MAHPERD's activities. Among the most notable is Michigan Exemplary Physical Education Programs Project Steering Committee (.5 linear foot), consisting of meeting minutes, memoranda, rosters, position statements, schedules, reports, evaluative instructional activities, games, lesson plans, and procedural guidelines. This file contains records which closely follow the implementation of k-12 physical education initiatives in Michigan. The file is arranged by year, 1986-1991. Of particular interest are the records generated in 1988, primarily documenting collaborative efforts between MEPEPP and Michigan Department of Education. Included in this series are goals and objectives, evaluative criteria, and instructional models.
  Midwest District of the American Alliance for Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance, contains one folder of records documenting the activities of this regional parent organization between 1980 and 1983. In addition, this series contains records documenting the work of state chapters other than Michigan.
  - Coaching
    - 1974-1975 (Box 6)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Cooperative Projects (Box 7)
    - Undated (Box 7)
    - 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Funding 1964-1971 (Box 7)
  - Health Resource Guide 1980 (Box 7)
  - Interscholastic Athletics 1978 (Box 7)
  - Jump-Rope-A-Thon 1980 (Box 7)
  - Legislation (Title IX) 1974 (Box 7)
  - Lifetime Sports Projects (Box 7)
  - Middle School Subject Matter, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Necrology (Box 7)
  - "Operation Pride," 1971 (Box 7)
  - Physical Education Survey 1968-1971 (Box 7)
  - Promotion 1964-1971 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Exemplary Physical Education Programs Project Steering Committee 1986-1988, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Michigan Exemplary Physical Education Programs Project 1989-1991, 1 notebook; 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Midwest District of the American Alliance for Health, Physical Education, Recreation, and Dance 1980-1983 (Box 11)
- Publications
  Publications consists of Correspondence, Editors' Reports, and an almost complete run of MAHPER official publications, from the MAHPER News (1960-1969) and the later MAHPER Journal (1970-1982). There are even a few of the early MAHPER Newsletters, from 1946-1959. The convention programs document the official tasks, studies, and activities of top priority for each particular year. The journals provide overviews of the development of MAHPERD goals and objectives. Additional MAHPERD publications consisting of special reports on activity planning and performance objectives, evaluative criteria, and educational guidelines, are included in the file "MAHPER. 1960-1979." Michigan Department of Education materials include education manuals, program standards, survey reports, and curricula models. MEPEPP materials include project overviews, survey and evaluation guidelines, and developmental handbooks and guides. The Midwest District AAHPERD materials consist of convention programs. The "Miscellaneous" file contains newsletters, special reports and journals created by outside agencies related to MAHPERD.
  - Correspondence 1969-1972 (Box 7)
  - Editor's Report (Box 7)
  - The MAHPER News
    - 1946-1969, 5 folders (Box 7)
  - The MAHPER Journal
    - 1970-1982, 6 folders (Box 7)
  - Miscellanea (Box 7)
  - MAHPER Convention Programs 1942-1991, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - MAHPER (various publications) 1960-1979 (Box 11)
  - MAHPER Journal 1983-1992, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Midwest District AAHPERD Convention Programs
    - 1975-1989 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Department of Education
    - 1974-1980 (Box 11)
    - 1987-1990 (Box 11)
  - MEPEPP Handbook for Consultants (Box 11)
  - Chin-up newsletter (Box 14)
  - Convention programs (Box 14)
  - Journal (Box 15)
- Reports, Scrapbooks and Miscellanea
  Reports that did not fit into other headings are located next, along with a Scrapbook of clippings and MAHPER announcements from 1955, and one folder of Miscellanea.
  - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 7)
  - Scrapbook (Box 7)
  - Miscellanea (Box 7)
  - Michigan Department of Education: Physical Education Interpretive Reports 1981-1982, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
- Photos
  The Photos series consists of five folder of prints of convention speakers and various officers. Photos in box 11 include four prints of MAHPERD officials. There are two pictures of Dr. Hal Ray, MAHPERD president 1986-1987, and pictures of two professors of health and physical education, Dr. Margaret S. Large, and Dr. Janet Wessel.
  - Photographs, 4 envelopes (Box 7)
  - Photographs (Box 11)
- Divisions 1970-1980
  - Dance 1971-1978 (Box 8)
  - Girls' and Women's Sports 1970-1974 (Box 8)
  - Health 1975-1978 (Box 8)
  - Physical Education/Public Image 1972-1980 (Box 8)
- President's Files 1967-
  - 1967-1989
    Presidents' Files (.75 linear foot) 1967-1989. The files have been arranged alphabetically. These topical files provide information about all aspects of the organization, (i.e. committees, districts, workshops, bylaws, etc.) and concentrate on the activities that took place during the years 1971-1974. Of special note is the correspondence file of Betty Menzi, who was a president of MAHPER in the early 1970s.
    - Agendas 1973-1974 (Box 8)
    - Annual Reports to National (AAPHER) 1967-1974 (Box 8)
    - Awards Committee 1972 (Box 8)
    - Blue Sky Committee 1978-1979 (Box 8)
    - Board of Directors lists 1972-1982 (Box 8)
    - Board Meeting Minutes and Agendas 1967-1987 (Box 8)
    - Budgets 1970-1978 (Box 9)
    - Candidates for Offices 1982 (Box 9)
    - Committee Lists 1972-1975 (Box 9)
    - Constitution and Constitution Committee 1967-1979 (Box 9)
    - Convention 1971-1982 (Box 9)
    - Council of State Organizations (COSO) 1972-1974 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence (Betty Menzi) 1967-1974 (Box 9)
    - Dance Division 1971-1973 (Box 9)
    - Date Sheets, undated-1982 (Box 9)
    - Delegates to be sent to Representative Assembly 1972-1974 (Box 9)
    - District Reports 1972-1973 (Box 9)